<resources>
    <string name="nc_text_get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="nc_text_welcome_to_nunchuk">Welcome to Nunchuk</string>
    <string name="nc_text_intro">Where private messaging meets the safest Bitcoin wallet.</string>
    <string name="nc_txt_message_function_require_an_account">Please create an account</string>
    <string name="nc_txt_message_function_require_des">Accounts are required for interpersonal messaging and collaborative wallet features.</string>
    <string name="nc_txt_guest_mode_got_it">Got it</string>
    <string name="nc_txt_guest_mode_intro_1">Guest mode allows you to create keys and wallets without an account. Please consider the following before using—</string>
    <string name="nc_txt_guest_mode_intro_2">Keys and wallets created in guest mode are stored locally. They will not be removed until you manually delete them or uninstall the app.</string>
    <string name="nc_txt_guest_mode_intro_3">Messaging and collaborative multisig wallets (*) are currently not available in guest mode.</string>
    <string name="nc_txt_guest_mode_intro_4">*A collaborative multisig wallet is a wallet where you co-manage bitcoin with other people.</string>
    <string name="nc_txt_guest_mode_header_1">1</string>
    <string name="nc_txt_guest_mode_header_2">2</string>
    <string name="nc_quick_create_a_hot_wallet_desc">Quickly create a hot wallet for immediate use and back it up later.</string>
    <string name="nc_create_a_hot_wallet_now">Create a hot wallet now</string>
    <string name="nc_i_ll_explore_on_my_own">I’ll explore on my own</string>
    <string name="nc_unassisted_wallet">Unassisted wallet</string>
    <string name="nc_unassisted_wallet_desc">Freely create hot wallets, watch-only wallets, or state-of-the-art multisig wallets that work with a plethora of hardware signing devices. Choose one that fits your need.</string>
    <string name="nc_assisted_wallet">Assisted wallet</string>
    <string name="nc_assisted_wallet_option_desc">For those who are new to Bitcoin, need expert guidance, or want advanced features such as inheritance planning or multi-user wallets.</string>
    <string name="nc_unassisted_wallet_option_desc">For those who are comfortable with doing everything themselves.</string>
    <string name="nc_how_will_you_use_nunchuk">How will you use Nunchuk?</string>
    <string name="nc_already_have_an_account_sign_in">Already have an account? [A]Sign in[/A]</string>
    <string name="nc_hot_wallet">Hot wallet</string>
    <string name="nc_hot_wallet_desc">A hot wallet is a wallet that is frequently connected to the Internet.\n\nFor securing large amounts of funds, consider moving to a cold wallet, a multisig wallet or an assisted multisig wallet for better security.</string>
    <string name="nc_learn_more_about_assisted_wallet">Learn more about assisted wallet</string>
    <string name="nc_send_query">Send query</string>
    <string name="nc_query_sent">Query sent</string>
    <string name="nc_have_an_advisor">I have an advisor</string>
    <string name="nc_have_advisor_desc">Your advisor should have sent you an invitation to join a group wallet. Please sign up for a new account and make sure to use the email address included in the invitation.\n\nIf you already signed up, please sign in.</string>
    <string name="nc_have_advisor_desc_logged_in">Your advisor should have sent you an invitation to join a group wallet. If you don’t see one yet, ask them to resend the invitation.</string>
    <string name="nc_your_country">Your country</string>
    <string name="nc_your_email_address">Your email address</string>
    <string name="nc_select_a_country">Select a country</string>
    <string name="nc_dont_have_an_advisor">I don’t have an advisor</string>
    <string name="nc_dont_have_an_advisor_desc">If you are looking for a white-glove, personalized service offered by a Bitcoin Advisor, enter your country and email address below, and we’ll send you the best Bitcoin Advisors in your area.\n\nAlternatively, check out the assisted services offered by our platform.</string>
    <string name="nc_learn_more_about_assisted_services">Learn more about Nunchuk assisted services</string>
    <string name="nc_onboard_assisted_wallet_intro_desc">An assisted wallet is a wallet that comes with expert guidance and help along every step of your Bitcoin journey, either from a qualified Bitcoin Advisor or our platform.\n\nHere are some of the things that you can do with an assisted wallet:</string>
</resources>
