<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="nc_signer_intro_title">Please add a key before adding a wallet.</string>
    <string name="nc_wallet_intro_title">Looks like you have added a key</string>
    <string name="nc_signer_intro_subtitle">NFC, air-gapped and software keys are supported.</string>
    <string name="nc_wallet_intro_subtitle">Do you want to add a Bitcoin wallet?</string>
    <string name="nc_text_add_a_signer">Add a key</string>
    <string name="nc_text_add_a_wallet">Add a wallet</string>

    <string name="nc_text_you_have_not_add_wallet">You have no wallets yet</string>
    <string name="nc_text_you_have_not_add_signer">You have no keys yet</string>
    <string name="nc_text_connection_status_offline">Offline</string>
    <string name="nc_text_connection_status_syncing">Syncing</string>
    <string name="nc_text_connection_status_online">Online</string>
    <string name="nc_text_home_wallet_chain_testnet">(Testnet)</string>
    <string name="nc_text_home_wallet_chain_signet">(Signet)</string>
    <string name="nc_text_home_wallet_connection">%s %s</string>
    <string name="nc_setup_satscard_msg">No active slot is detected. Do you want to set up a new slot?</string>
    <string name="nc_assisted_wallet_intro_desc">This wizard will walk you through creating an assisted wallet step by step.</string>
    <string name="nc_you_almost_done">You’re almost done!</string>
    <string name="nc_continue_setting_your_wallet">Continue setting up your wallet</string>
    <string name="nc_error_co_signing_delay_empty">Please input co-signing delay</string>
    <string name="nc_inheritance_plan_title">Thinking about setting up an inheritance plan?</string>
    <string name="nc_restart_wizard">Restart wizard</string>
    <string name="nc_exit_wizard">Exit wizard</string>
    <string name="nc_resume_wizard_desc">You can resume the wizard anytime from the Wallets tab.</string>
    <string name="nc_inheritance_intro_hint">TAPSIGNER is a wireless NFC smart card that will sign transactions with a simple tap on your phone.</string>
    <string name="nc_tapsigner">TAPSIGNER</string>
    <string name="nc_coldcard">COLDCARD</string>
    <string name="nc_add_coldcard_via_nfc">Add COLDCARD via NFC</string>
    <string name="nc_cosigning_limit_hint">If you have configured a co-signing spending limit for the platform key, it is safe to carry one key with you. Use two of your own keys when you want to withdraw more than the limit.</string>
    <string name="nc_register_wallet_to_airgap_title">Please register this wallet with your air-gapped device</string>
    <string name="nc_register_wallet_to_airgap_desc">You must register this wallet with your air-gapped device before you can use it to sign transactions.\n\nPlease do so by scanning the QR code on the next screen using your device.</string>
    <string name="nc_inheritance_claim_trustee">The inheritance can be claimed directly by the Beneficiary or indirectly through a third-party Trustee.</string>
    <string name="nc_plan_overview">Plan overview</string>
    <string name="nc_plan_overview_desc">The inheritance plan will have these main components:</string>
    <string name="nc_activation_date">An activation date</string>
    <string name="nc_plan_overview_bottom_desc">We will now go through them one-by-one.</string>
    <string name="nc_find_backup_password_desc">In your wallet, you have designated a TAPSIGNER to be the inheritance key. An encrypted backup of this key is stored on our server.\n\nOn or after the activation date, the Beneficiary or Trustee can recover this key using the Backup Password printed on the back of the TAPSIGNER (it might be listed under “Backup key”).\n\n[B]Make note of this Backup Password[/B]. You will need to share it with the Beneficiary or Trustee.</string>
    <string name="nc_find_backup_password">Find your Backup Password</string>
    <string name="nc_set_up_inheritance_hint">[B]Beneficiary[/B]: an individual who will inherit your bitcoin.\n\n[B]Trustee[/B]: an individual who will help manage and distribute your bitcoin to the Beneficiary.</string>
    <string name="nc_here_is_plan_magical_phrase">Here is your plan’s Magic Phrase</string>
    <string name="nc_inheritance_key_tip">Inheritance key tip</string>
    <string name="nc_dummy_transaction_desc">To authorize these changes, two signatures are required. You will be asked to sign a dummy transaction that sends 10,000 sats (%1$s) to your own wallet.\n\n[B]The dummy transaction uses a fake input and does not move any of your real Bitcoins. It will not be broadcast and will immediately removed afterwards.[/B]</string>
    <string name="nc_tell_me_more">Tell me more</string>
    <string name="nc_try_on_testnet">Try on testnet</string>
    <string name="nc_try_assisted_wallet_desc">All Bitcoin features work exactly the same on testnet as they would on the real blockchain. See if an assisted wallet is a good fit for you by trying it out on testnet.</string>
    <string name="nc_try_assisted_wallet_hint">The testnet is an alternative Bitcoin blockchain used for testing. Testnet coins are separate and distinct from actual bitcoins and they do not hold any value.</string>
</resources>