<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="nc_signer_intro_title">Please add a key before adding a wallet.</string>
    <string name="nc_wallet_intro_title">Looks like you have added a key</string>
    <string name="nc_signer_intro_subtitle">NFC, air-gapped and software keys are supported.</string>
    <string name="nc_wallet_intro_subtitle">Do you want to add a Bitcoin wallet?</string>
    <string name="nc_text_add_a_signer">Add a key</string>
    <string name="nc_text_add_a_wallet">Add a wallet</string>

    <string name="nc_text_you_have_not_add_wallet">You have no wallets yet</string>
    <string name="nc_text_you_have_not_add_signer">You have no keys yet</string>
    <string name="nc_text_connection_status_offline">Offline</string>
    <string name="nc_text_connection_status_syncing">Syncing</string>
    <string name="nc_text_connection_status_online">Online</string>
    <string name="nc_text_home_wallet_chain_testnet">(Testnet)</string>
    <string name="nc_text_home_wallet_chain_signet">(Signet)</string>
    <string name="nc_text_home_wallet_connection">%s %s</string>
    <string name="nc_setup_satscard_msg">No active slot is detected. Do you want to set up a new slot?</string>
    <string name="nc_assisted_wallet_intro_desc">This wizard will walk you through creating an assisted wallet step by step.</string>
    <string name="nc_you_almost_done">You’re almost done!</string>
    <string name="nc_error_co_signing_delay_empty">Please input co-signing delay</string>
    <string name="nc_inheritance_plan_title">Thinking about setting up an inheritance plan?</string>
    <string name="nc_inheritance_intro_hint">TAPSIGNER is a wireless NFC smart card that will sign transactions with a simple tap on your phone.</string>
    <string name="nc_tapsigner">TAPSIGNER</string>
    <string name="nc_add_coldcard_via_nfc">Add COLDCARD via NFC</string>
    <string name="nc_register_wallet_to_airgap_title">Please register this wallet with your air-gapped device</string>
    <string name="nc_register_wallet_to_airgap_desc">You must register this wallet with your air-gapped device before you can use it to sign transactions.\n\nPlease do so by scanning the QR code on the next screen using your device.</string>
    <string name="nc_inheritance_claim_trustee">The inheritance can be claimed directly by the Beneficiary or indirectly through a third-party Trustee.</string>
    <string name="nc_plan_overview">Plan overview</string>
    <string name="nc_plan_overview_desc">The inheritance plan will have these main components:</string>
    <string name="nc_activation_date">Activation Date</string>
    <string name="nc_plan_overview_bottom_desc">We will now go through them one-by-one.</string>
    <string name="nc_find_backup_password_desc">In your wallet, you have designated a TAPSIGNER to be the inheritance key. An encrypted backup of this key is stored on our server.\n\nOn or after the activation date, the Beneficiary or Trustee can recover this key using the Backup Password printed on the back of the TAPSIGNER (it might be listed under “Backup key”).\n\n[B]Make note of this Backup Password[/B]. You will need to share it with the Beneficiary or Trustee.</string>
    <string name="nc_find_backup_password">Find your Backup Password</string>
    <string name="nc_set_up_inheritance_hint">[B]Beneficiary[/B]: an individual who will inherit your bitcoin.\n\n[B]Trustee[/B]: an individual who will help manage and distribute your bitcoin to the Beneficiary.</string>
    <string name="nc_here_is_plan_magical_phrase">Here is your plan’s Magic Phrase</string>
    <string name="nc_inheritance_key_tip">Inheritance key tip</string>
    <string name="nc_dummy_transaction_desc">To authorize these changes, two signatures are required. You will be asked to sign a dummy transaction that sends 10,000 sats (%1$s) to your own wallet.\n\n[B]The dummy transaction uses a fake input and does not move any of your real bitcoins. It will not be broadcast and will be immediately removed afterwards.[/B]</string>
    <string name="nc_tell_me_more">Tell me more</string>
    <string name="nc_try_on_testnet">Try on testnet</string>
    <string name="nc_try_assisted_wallet_desc">All Bitcoin features work exactly the same on testnet as they would on the real blockchain. See if an assisted wallet is a good fit for you by trying it out on testnet.</string>
    <string name="nc_try_assisted_wallet_hint">The testnet is an alternative Bitcoin blockchain used for testing. Testnet coins are separate and distinct from actual bitcoins and they do not hold any value.</string>
    <string name="nc_hint_config_spending_limit">You can bypass the spending limit by signing transactions using two of your own keys.</string>
    <string name="nc_key_reuse_desc">Do you want to reuse the keys from one of the existing assisted wallets?</string>
    <string name="nc_seedsigner">SeedSigner</string>
    <string name="nc_main_add_ledger_desc">To use Ledger with your assisted wallet, you will need the desktop app. If you don’t have it yet, please [A]download it here[/A].\n\nOnce the app is installed, sign in to your account on desktop, then click Continue below.</string>
    <string name="nc_main_add_trezor_desc">To use Trezor with your assisted wallet, you will need the desktop app. If you don’t have it yet, please [A]download it here[/A].\n\nOnce the app is installed, sign in to your account on desktop, then click Continue below.</string>
    <string name="nc_main_add_coldcard_desc">To add COLDCARD via a USB cable, you will need the desktop app. If you don’t have it yet, please [A]download it here[/A].\n\nOnce the app is installed, sign in to your account on desktop, then click Continue below.</string>
    <string name="nc_main_add_bitbox_desc">To use BitBox with your assisted wallet, you will need the desktop app. If you don’t have it yet, please [A]download it here[/A].\n\nOnce the app is installed, sign in to your account on desktop, then click Continue below.</string>
    <string name="nc_add_desktop_key">Add %1$s</string>
    <string name="nc_i_have_already_added_desktop_key">I have already added %1$s</string>
    <string name="nc_waiting_for_desktop_key_to_be_added">Waiting for %1$s to be added</string>
    <string name="nc_add_key_using_desktop_desc">You can now add %1$s using the desktop app. Once finished, you can return here to continue the setup.</string>
    <string name="nc_ledger">Ledger</string>
    <string name="nc_trezor">Trezor</string>
    <string name="nc_bitbox">BitBox</string>
    <string name="nc_add_trezor">Add Trezor</string>
    <string name="nc_no_device_have_been_detected">No %1$s devices have been detected. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="nc_added_successfully">%1$s added successfully</string>
    <string name="nc_add_coldcard_via_usb">Add COLDCARD via USB</string>
    <string name="nc_what_is_a_group_wallet">What is a group wallet?</string>
    <string name="nc_group_wallet_intro">A Nunchuk group wallet is a multisig wallet where multiple people share control of the wallet. Keys can be distributed among the master account and a secondary account, or secondary accounts.\n\nDepending on your preference, the platform can also hold one additional key to assist in inheritance planning and the daily operation of the wallet.</string>
    <string name="nc_security_trade_off_desc">On one hand, having multiple people involved in a wallet means that the burden of key management can be shared. The keys are also more likely to be well distributed.\n\nOn the other hand, since members’ skill levels typically vary, it also means that it is harder to guarantee the security of the individual keys. Each member must take care to protect their own key.\n\nWhen in doubt, [B]lean towards having fewer keyholders in a group wallet[/B]. If your use case demands multiple keyholders, please make sure that all members understand their rights and responsibilities.</string>
    <string name="nc_2_of_4_multisig_title">2-of-4 multisig with inheritance planning</string>
    <string name="nc_2_of_3_multisig_title">2-of-3 multisig without inheritance planning</string>
    <string name="nc_3_of_5_multisig_title">3-of-5 multisig without inheritance planning</string>
    <string name="nc_2_of_4_multisig_desc">A master account and secondary account(s) control three keys; Nunchuk holds the fourth key on our secure server to assist in inheritance planning and daily wallet operation.</string>
    <string name="nc_2_of_3_multisig_desc">A master account and secondary account(s) control three keys; Nunchuk does not control any keys.</string>
    <string name="nc_3_of_5_multisig_desc">A master account and secondary account(s) control five keys; Nunchuk does not control any keys.</string>
    <string name="nc_main_select_group_wallet_type">Select group wallet type</string>
    <string name="nc_main_what_type_of_group_wallet">What type of group wallet do you want to create?</string>
    <string name="nc_main_wallet_setup_preference">Wallet setup preference</string>
    <string name="nc_wallet_setup_preference_desc">What is your preferred method for setting up this group wallet?</string>
    <string name="nc_main_option_single_person_setup_desc">Single-person setup: the master account creates the wallet then distributes key(s) to group members.</string>
    <string name="nc_main_distributed_setup_desc">Distributed setup: the group members hold key(s) from the start and partipate in the creation of the wallet.</string>
    <string name="nc_main_wallet_setup_preference_hint">Only use a single-person setup if all members in the group are able to trust the master account to handle keys on their behalf.\t\t\t</string>
    <string name="nc_apply_the_same_limit">Apply the same limit to all members</string>
    <string name="nc_invite_members">Invite members</string>
    <string name="nc_invite_members_desc">Enter the members’ emails and roles. You can have up to 3 keyholders (including the master account) and 3 observers.</string>
    <string name="nc_member_data">Member %s</string>
    <string name="nc_email_address">Email address</string>
    <string name="nc_add_more_members">Add more members</string>
    <string name="nc_role">Role</string>
    <string name="nc_keyholder_admin">Keyholder (admin)</string>
    <string name="nc_keyholder_admin_desc">Can make changes to inheritance planning and wallet policies.\nCan add or remove group members.\nCan edit transaction notes, create coin tags or collections.\nCan create and sign transactions.\nCan view wallet transactions.\nCan participate in group chat.</string>
    <string name="nc_keyholder">Keyholder</string>
    <string name="nc_keyholder_desc">Can create and sign transactions.\nCan view wallet transactions.\nCan participate in group chat.</string>
    <string name="nc_observer">Observer</string>
    <string name="nc_observer_desc">Can view wallet transactions, but no signing privileges.\nCan participate in group chat.</string>
    <string name="nc_select_a_role">Select a role</string>
    <string name="nc_members">Members</string>
    <string name="nc_members_updated">Members updated</string>
    <string name="nc_three_keyholder_setup_message_dialog">If each keyholder holds their own key, all members will have equal rights in the wallet. At any point in time, two of the keyholders can withdraw all bitcoins without the remaining person’s permission.\nAre you sure you want this setup?</string>
    <string name="nc_admin_role_message_dialog">The admin account will have the ability to change the inheritance planning, wallet policies and group membership. Please make sure that it is someone that you can trust.</string>
    <string name="nc_primary_key_admin_role_message_dialog">An admin must have an email-based account.</string>
    <string name="nc_limit_keyholder_message_dialog">Please make sure that you have no more than 3 keyholders.</string>
    <string name="nc_byzantine_add_key_desc">Your new wallet will be a 2-of-4 multisig wallet. [B]Two keys are always required for spending[/B].\n\nYour group will have possession of three keys. The fourth key will be held by Nunchuk on our secure server.\n\nAmong your three keys, select one key to be the inheritance key. It must be a TAPSIGNER.\n\nPull to refresh the key statuses.</string>
    <string name="nc_pending_wallet">Pending wallet</string>
    <string name="nc_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="nc_deny">Deny</string>
    <string name="nc_alert">Alert</string>
    <string name="nc_pending_wallet_invite_member">%s invited you to join a group wallet.</string>
    <string name="nc_view_recurring_payments">View recurring payments</string>
    <string name="nc_manage_group_chat_history">Manage group chat history</string>
    <string name="nc_chat_setting_updated">Chat setting updated</string>
    <string name="nc_keep_group_chat_history">Keep group chat history for:</string>
    <string name="nc_deny_wallet_invitation_dialog">Are you sure you want to deny this wallet invitation?</string>
    <string name="nc_deny_wallet_invitation_msg">Wallet invitation has been denied</string>
    <string name="nc_group_wallet_creation_pending">Group wallet creation pending</string>
    <string name="nc_group_wallet_creation_pending_desc">%s initiated a group wallet. If you’re part of this wallet, please add your key.</string>
</resources>